<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ananke: a Hugo Theme on Ananke</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ananke: a Hugo Theme on Ananke</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of&#xA;this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on&#xA;by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to&#xA;listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined&#xA;to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on&#xA;the part of the public. This gleam of hope acquired fresh life, when he&#xA;saw Quasimodo, Coppenole, and the deafening escort of the pope of the&#xA;procession of fools quit the hall amid great uproar. The throng rushed&#xA;eagerly after them. “Good,” he said to himself, “there go all the&#xA;mischief-makers.” Unfortunately, all the mischief-makers constituted the&#xA;entire audience. In the twinkling of an eye, the grand hall was empty.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter V: Quasimodo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the twinkling of an eye, all was ready to execute Coppenole’s idea. Bourgeois, scholars and law clerks all set to work. The little chapel situated opposite the marble table was selected for the scene of the grinning match. A pane broken in the pretty rose window above the door, left free a circle of stone through which it was agreed that the competitors should thrust their heads. In order to reach it, it was only necessary to mount upon a couple of hogsheads, which had been produced from I know not where, and perched one upon the other, after a fashion. It was settled that each candidate, man or woman (for it was possible to choose a female pope), should, for the sake of leaving the impression of his grimace fresh and complete, cover his face and remain concealed in the chapel until the moment of his appearance. In less than an instant, the chapel was crowded with competitors, upon whom the door was then closed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low&#xA;bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a&#xA;large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter&#xA;abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by&#xA;the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the&#xA;velvet and silk which surrounded him. Presuming that he was some groom who&#xA;had stolen in, the usher stopped him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Monsieur the Cardinal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean,&#xA;the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that&#xA;famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris,&#xA;on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians&#xA;at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the&#xA;Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic&#xA;moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His&#xA;eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration&#xA;unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when&#xA;he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence,&#xA;the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder&#xA;of hooting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the&#xA;people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was&#xA;audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence&#xA;instantly!” yelped the scholar.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago&#xA;to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple&#xA;circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has&#xA;preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus&#xA;set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.&#xA;It was neither an assault by the Picards nor the Burgundians, nor a hunt&#xA;led along in procession, nor a revolt of scholars in the town of Laas, nor&#xA;an entry of “our much dread lord, monsieur the king,” nor even a pretty&#xA;hanging of male and female thieves by the courts of Paris. Neither was it&#xA;the arrival, so frequent in the fifteenth century, of some plumed and&#xA;bedizened embassy. It was barely two days since the last cavalcade of that&#xA;nature, that of the Flemish ambassadors charged with concluding the&#xA;marriage between the dauphin and Marguerite of Flanders, had made its&#xA;entry into Paris, to the great annoyance of M. le Cardinal de Bourbon,&#xA;who, for the sake of pleasing the king, had been obliged to assume an&#xA;amiable mien towards this whole rustic rabble of Flemish burgomasters, and&#xA;to regale them at his Hôtel de Bourbon, with a very “pretty morality,&#xA;allegorical satire, and farce,” while a driving rain drenched the&#xA;magnificent tapestries at his door.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Victor_Hugo-Hunchback.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h4&gt;Illustration from Victor Hugo et son temps (1881)&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Hunchback of Notre-Dame&lt;/em&gt; (French: &lt;em&gt;Notre-Dame de Paris&lt;/em&gt;) is a French Romantic/Gothic novel by Victor Hugo, published in 1831. The original French title refers to Notre Dame Cathedral, on which the story is centered. English translator Frederic Shoberl named the novel The Hunchback of Notre Dame in 1833 because at the time, Gothic novels were more popular than Romance novels in England. The story is set in Paris, France in the Late Middle Ages, during the reign of Louis XI.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the shortcode to make it work. Check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://formspree.io/&#34;&gt;Formspree&lt;/a&gt; for a simple, free form service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;form class=&#34;black-80 sans-serif&#34; accept-charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34; action=&#34;https://example.com&#34; method=&#34;POST&#34; role=&#34;form&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;label class=&#34;f6 b db mb1 mt3 sans-serif mid-gray&#34;  for=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Your Name&lt;/label&gt;&#xA;    &lt;input type=&#34;text&#34; id=&#34;name&#34; name=&#34;name&#34; class=&#34;w-100 f5 pv3 ph3 bg-light-gray bn&#34;  required placeholder=&#34; &#34;  aria-labelledby=&#34;name&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;label class=&#34;f6 b db mb1 mt3 sans-serif mid-gray&#34; for=&#34;email&#34;&gt;Email Address&lt;/label&gt;&#xA;    &lt;input type=&#34;email&#34; id=&#34;email&#34; name=&#34;email&#34; class=&#34;w-100 f5 pv3 ph3 bg-light-gray bn&#34;  required placeholder=&#34; &#34;  aria-labelledby=&#34;email&#34;/&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;requirements f6 gray glow i ph3 overflow-hidden&#34;&gt;&#xA;      An email address is required.&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;label class=&#34;f6 b db mb1 mt3 sans-serif mid-gray&#34; for=&#34;message&#34;&gt;Message&lt;/label&gt;&#xA;    &lt;textarea id=&#34;message&#34; name=&#34;message&#34; class=&#34;w-100 f5 pv3 ph3 bg-light-gray bn h4&#34; aria-labelledby=&#34;message&#34;&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;input class=&#34;db w-100 mv2 white pa3 bn hover-shadow hover-bg-black bg-animate bg-black&#34; type=&#34;submit&#34; value=&#34;Send&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/form&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
